<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Starting an Audit :: Fusion CAC Documentation</title>
    <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/auditor-user-guide/starting-an-audit/</link>
    <description>Ensure you have the role of an auditor and chart access of auditor. Open a chart that has been submitted by a coder, you may get this chart from a worklist or, by manually typing in an account number. On the navigation tree you will notice a viewer called “Audit Worksheet”. Click on “Start Audit” to begin Upon clicking on “start audit”, select your audit type from the dropdown. This will be used for reporting on the types of audit you performed, and this can also be used for workflow purposes. The codes in the “assigned code” tree are the same codes initially submitted by the coder, allowing the auditor to start the audit with the codes from the coder. The audit viewer can be popped out onto a separate screen, allowing the auditor to have a screen for reviewing the chart. By selecting “Show All” codes in the unassigned code tree, the auditor is taken to the documents/documentation supporting that code. This will help streamline the audit process. Once the auditor has made changes and is completed with the audit, they can click “Update Codes” which automatically calculates and populates the audit statistics section. There is a comment bubble next to each code as well as the DRG for the auditor to enter any comment. Next to the codes a symbol may display. A green ‘plus’ sign will show if the code was added. A red ‘minus’ sign will show if a code was deleted. A orange up or down ‘arrow’ sign will appear if the code location has been changed, as in a primary and secondary are swapped. Although audit statistics have been automatically calculated and populated, the auditor must manually enter in the “total errors” which then automatically calculates the “Error Rate”. Complete the additional sections, (abstracting and training recommendations) if applicable. The auditor can then re-submit the chart or route it back to the coder of record by using the “Route to Coder” button in the top right corner of the audit worksheet. This will route the chart to the coder’s “You” worklist for them to review and re-submit.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/auditor-user-guide/starting-an-audit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  </channel>
</rss>