<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cds User Guide :: Fusion CAC Documentation</title>
    <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/</link>
    <description>This program will introduce automatic workflow processes which is defined as processes where tasks, information or documents are passed from one place to another for action, according to a set of procedural rules.&#xA;Each organization will have different workflows from one another to coordinate tasks between people and synchronize data between systems, with the ultimate goal of improving organizational efficiency and responsiveness.&#xA;Each CDS will have a worklist which will include new cases if current patient location meets the CDS work assignments and follow-up cases that the chart owner has been assigned for the CDS reviewing.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chart Reviews</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/chart-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/chart-reviews/</guid>
      <description>There are 3 different types of reviews:&#xA;Initial Follow-up Reconciliation Initial Review An initial review is a new case in terms of ‘CDI’ and is referred to as a case that has never been reviewed by CDI. A CDI review for inpatient charts must have a working DRG associated to be considered reviewed. If there is no DRG then the patient is considered new.&#xA;When a CDI Specialist creates a Baseline DRG (the first Working DRG), then edits the account further causing the Working DRG to be cleared, and then saves the account without computing a new Working DRG, the creation of the Baseline DRG also counts as an initial review.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDI Alerts and Chart Prioritization</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/chart-prioritization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/chart-prioritization/</guid>
      <description>The software has a feature called CDI Alerts which are automated messages generated by the software that can be used to prioritize your CDI workflow. CDI Alerts are used to detect potential inaccuracies, inconsistencies and or discrepancies in clinical documentation. These Alerts help CDI teams to prioritize the charts based on potential query opportunities available.&#xA;The software provides real-time Alerts when potential query opportunities are identified. Which will then allow CDI staff to prioritize charts based upon those potential opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Receiving Credit for Reviews</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/receiving-credit-for-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/receiving-credit-for-reviews/</guid>
      <description>Receiving Credit for Reviews Review Type Details Initial Review For Inpatient charts this is the first time a working DRG is computed and saved on a chart by a user with the role of CDI. For outpatient this is the first time a chart is opened and saved by a user with the role of CDI. Follow-up Review For Inpatient charts this any subsequent time after the initial a chart is accessed a working DRG is computed and saved on a chart by a user with the role of CDI however, a chart is only counted 1 time per day. For outpatient this is the first time a chart is opened and saved by a user with the role of CDI however, a chart is only counted 1 time per day Reconciliation Reconciliation can only happen 1 time per chart, so pass back and forth do not count. Query Completion This is counted as a Subsequent or Follow-up Review. Documentation Reviews If your site does different styles of CDI reviews or want to track management reporting there are reports for documentation reviews, different than how our default tracks, you can use the documentation review viewer to track reviews by topic. Other organizations have used this if there CDI team would like to do a utilization management type review and it doesn’t fit the typical initial or follow up review.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Review Date</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/next-review-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/next-review-date/</guid>
      <description>Next Review Date field can be changed to a different date other than the default which is every day. A CDS can change the interval that the chart is routed back to a queue, when on the code summary page changing the calendar date field from the date displayed to a future date. This will tell the chart to not route back to the “Follow-up Review” until the current calendar date matches the date you changed the next review date to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matched Criteria</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/matched-criteria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/matched-criteria/</guid>
      <description>CDI Users Only The Matched Criteria viewer is only shown if your current role is CDI.&#xA;Matched criteria allow you to see why the chart was routed to you. The matched criteria group is a list of “criteria group” that the chart matched upon when it went through workflow. These criteria groups are used to indicate a “possible” query opportunity based upon the criteria outlined in workflow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query Impact</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/query-impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/query-impact/</guid>
      <description>How does the impact of a query get recorded? The impact for inpatient cases is captured by the natural actions a CDS takes, therefore no manual data entry needs to be tracked by the CDS. The impact of the query is calculated by using the working DRG calculated within the same session in which you created the physician query for. Then once the physician replies to the query the CDS will then close the query as agreed, disagreed or no opinion. The same session that a CDS closes the query the system will then capture the working DRG that was calculated during this session. A session is closed by saving the chart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseline Drg</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/baseline-drg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/baseline-drg/</guid>
      <description>The baseline DRG is used for reporting program impact, some organizations do report like this, and others do not the choice is yours our system accommodates for it if you choose to use it. There are two styles of impact that can be reported which are:&#xA;Chart Impact Query Impact These are both reporting separately as you could be query positive impact regardless of if the chart has a positive, negative or neutral impact. The baseline is defined as the DRG that would have been coded and billed if no CDI specialist reviewed the chart.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>