<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Custom Fields :: Fusion CAC Documentation</title>
    <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/fields/custom-fields/</link>
    <description>The following table lists common fields that are implemented on an as-needed basis depending on requirements and licensing.&#xA;Display Name Field Description Charge CPT Codes Computed as a list of CPT codes assigned to Charges. Does not apply to Transactions. Charge Revenue Codes Computed as a list of Revenue Codes assigned to Charges. Does not apply to Transactions. Is Prior HCC Present Computed as True if any prior account of the patient contains an HCC code. Field is defined in the site’s ADT script and performs a database lookup upon receipt of ADT for prior accounts. Last Suggested Calculation Date/Time This is the last suggested DRG calculation date and time. The site must be licensed to use Suggested DRG Module. Last Suggested DRG This is the last suggested DRG. Site must be licensed to use Suggested DRG Module. Last Suggested DRG Description This is the last suggested DRG Description. Site must be licensed to use Suggested DRG Module. Last Suggested DRG Weight This is the last suggested DRG Weight. Site must be licensed to use Suggested DRG Module. Last Suggested Estimated Reimbursement This is the last suggested DRG Estimated Reimbursement. Site must be licensed to use Suggested DRG Module. PSI Indicator This is the PSI’s that were identified by a coder user. The PSI indicator is identified by using the patient safety indicator technical specifications. This field requires the quality module. Quality Measure This is a field used to identified if a coder user identified PC-06. The PC-06 indicator is identified by using the quality measures technical specifications. This field requires the quality module. CDI PSI Indicator This is the PSI’s that were identified by a CDI user. The PSI indicator is identified by using the patient safety indicator technical specifications. This field requires the quality module. CDI Quality Measure This is a field used to identified if a CDI user identified PC-06. The PC- 06 indicator is identified by using the quality measures technical specifications. This field requires the quality module</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/fields/custom-fields/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  </channel>
</rss>