<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abstracting :: Fusion CAC Documentation</title>
    <link>https://example.org/fields/abstracting/index.html</link>
    <description>Field Field Description Discharge Disposition Changed? This is a true or false field. If the Discharge Disposition was changed from the previous Disposition assignment the field will result in true which is counted as one error and if it was not changed it will result in false which is not counted as an error. N/A is available in the event the auditor wants to list it as not applicable to the audit. Abstracting Pre-Audit The total is the number of abstracting components there were at the time the audit is started. Abstractions Pre-Audit = (Total Procedure and CPT Codes x 2) + 1 for Discharge Disposition + 1 for Consulting Providers if Present). Procedure and CPT Codes are multiplied by two since there are to abstraction opportunities which is date of service and preforming provider. Abstracting Errors This is the total codes that appear in the above boxes the formula is as followed: Abstracting Errors = Procedure (PCS/CPT) Date Changes + Procedure (PCS/CPT) Provider Changes + Discharge Disposition Changes + Consulting Provider Changes. Abstracting Error Rate This is the total abstracting error rate as a percentage the formula is: Abstracting Errors = Procedure (PCS/CPT) Date Changes + Procedure (PCS/CPT) Provider Changes + Discharge Disposition Changes + Consulting Provider Changes/Abstracting Pre-Audit. Abstracting Accuracy Rate This is the total abstracting accuracy as a percentage the formula is: Abstracting Error Rate = (Procedure (PCS/CPT) Date Changes + Procedure (PCS/CPT) Provider Changes + Discharge Disposition Changes + Consulting Provider Changes/Abstracting Pre-Audit) – 100%.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/fields/abstracting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  </channel>
</rss>