<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coding a Patient Chart :: Fusion CAC Documentation</title>
    <link>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/index.html</link>
    <description>Loading Accounts Reviewing Documents Managing Codes Computing a Drg Account Screen Account Viewers Code Summary Patient Info Notes and Bookmarks Physicians and Queries Physician Coding Summary Final Coding Summary Working CDI History Suggested DRG Viewer Discrete Values and Flow Sheet Viewers Charges/Transactions Viewer Medications Viewers DRG Reconciliation Viewer 30 Day Readmit Previous HCC Overview Transfer Codes From Previous Encounter Viewer Denial Management Viewer ER E/M Viewer Document Tree Code Panels Exiting an Account</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Loading Accounts</title>
      <link>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/loading-accounts/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/loading-accounts/index.html</guid>
      <description>Assigned Accounts Grid Column Settings Each column within the Assigned Accounts Grid has menu options to pin, auto size, and reset columns as well as a Tool Panel to select which columns you want displayed in your view of the assigned accounts grid.&#xA;Click on the Menu icon to view the drop-down listing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing Documents</title>
      <link>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/reviewing-documents/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/reviewing-documents/index.html</guid>
      <description>Documents presented in Fusion CAC should be reviewed to determine the specific reason for the encounter and the conditions treated. Codes can be validated through document review from the Documents Pane or code review from the Unassigned Codes pane. Codes can also be added manually via direct code entry or through use of an interfaced encoder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Codes</title>
      <link>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/adding-codes/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/adding-codes/index.html</guid>
      <description>Upon opening the account for initial coding review, all the engine suggested codes will be listed in the Unassigned pane on the right-hand side under the Assigned Codes pane.&#xA;Codes are placed into the following categories:&#xA;Diagnosis Codes Procedure Codes CPT® Codes From here, you can right-click on a code, then either Assign or Edit/Assign the selected code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computing a Drg</title>
      <link>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/computing-a-drg/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/computing-a-drg/index.html</guid>
      <description>Use the Compute button to launch the encoder and proceed with confirmation of codes and sequencing to complete grouping and return the computed grouping and codes to Fusion CAC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Account Screen</title>
      <link>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/account-screen/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/account-screen/index.html</guid>
      <description>Banner Bar Below the Accounts Action Bar is the Banner Bar.&#xA;From the Banner Bar, you can toggle between account demographic information and Primary DRG information by clicking on the Primary DRG hyperlink. The DRG view displays information available from the encoder for the computed DRG. You can also click on the Patient Name to expand collapse the account demographic and DRG information. The Accounts Info bar includes information on the account including:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Account Viewers</title>
      <link>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/account-viewers/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/account-viewers/index.html</guid>
      <description>Account Viewers are located under the “Navigation” header, and give different views/information on the loaded account that are not contained in documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document Tree</title>
      <link>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/document-tree/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/document-tree/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Documents Pane frames the Documents Tree and is located on the left-hand side of the Account Screen. The Documents Tree includes a listing of all documents in a patient chart categorized by document type as configured by the hospital.&#xA;Icons next to document names in the Documents Tree indicate document types. Each document in the Documents Tree uses an icon or bolding to give information about the document. Listed below are Document Indicators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Panels</title>
      <link>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/code-panels/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/code-panels/index.html</guid>
      <description>Unassigned Codes Panel Diagnosis Codes In the bottom right panel on the screen, is a list of unassigned Diagnosis Codes that have been suggested by the engine for validation. Left-clicking on the diagnosis code will take you to the location within the document that prompted the code suggestion.&#xA;Procedure Codes Under unassigned Diagnosis Codes are listed all unassigned Procedure Codes that have been suggested by the engine for validation. Left-clicking on the procedure code will take you to the location within the document that prompted the code suggestion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exiting an Account</title>
      <link>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/exiting-an-account/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/coding-user-guide/coding-a-patient-chart/exiting-an-account/index.html</guid>
      <description>Once you have finished working in an account, there are three ways of proceeding&#xA;Cancel - This cancels all work in the chart and either returns to the Workgroup or autoloads the next account (if autoload is selected). Upon canceling if you have unsaved changes you will be prompted. Save - This saves your work and either returns to the Workgroup or autoloads the next account (if autoload is selected.) Submit - This saves and sends your work to the next phase of workflow, based on your organizations requirements and either returns to the Workgroup or autoloads the next account (if autoload is selected). Account Changed Warning Box</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>