<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fusion CAC User Guide :: Fusion CAC Documentation</title>
    <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/</link>
    <description>Welcome to the Fusion CAC Web Application Product Documentation site!&#xA;This site is intended for reference by coders, CDS as well as supervisors and technical users who need to understand CAC functionality and workflow. This document will explain how to use Fusion CAC, describe each CAC component’s functionality, identify best practices, and illustrate the benefits provided.&#xA;The various chapters within this guide can be navigated using the &lt; (previous) and &gt; (next) buttons at the top-right of your screen, the navigation list on the left, or the search box above the navigation.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Connected</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/getting-connected/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/getting-connected/</guid>
      <description>Fusion CAC is a browser-based program. To launch the CAC browser application, open your web browser and enter your site’s Fusion CAC server address into the browser address bar. You will need to get the Fusion CAC server address from your site administrator or manager.&#xA;Fusion CAC URL Example https://fusion-cac-production/cac2&#xA;This address is just an example. The address for your server will be different.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding User Guide</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/coding-user-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/coding-user-guide/</guid>
      <description>This guide explains the Fusion CAC Web application from the perspective of a coder.&#xA;Account List Coding a Patient Chart Loading Accounts Reviewing Documents Managing Codes Computing a Drg Account Screen Account Viewers Code Summary Patient Info Notes and Bookmarks Physicians and Queries Physician Coding Summary Final Coding Summary Working CDI History Suggested DRG Viewer Discrete Values and Flow Sheet Viewers Charges/Transactions Viewer Medications Viewers DRG Reconciliation Viewer 30 Day Readmit Previous HCC Overview Transfer Codes From Previous Encounter Viewer Denial Management Viewer ER E/M Viewer Document Tree Code Panels Exiting an Account</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cds User Guide</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/cds-user-guide/</guid>
      <description>This program will introduce automatic workflow processes which is defined as processes where tasks, information or documents are passed from one place to another for action, according to a set of procedural rules.&#xA;Each organization will have different workflows from one another to coordinate tasks between people and synchronize data between systems, with the ultimate goal of improving organizational efficiency and responsiveness.&#xA;Each CDS will have a worklist which will include new cases if current patient location meets the CDS work assignments and follow-up cases that the chart owner has been assigned for the CDS reviewing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auditor User Guide</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/auditor-user-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/auditor-user-guide/</guid>
      <description>The audit worksheet is a comprehensive module designed to streamline and enhance the coder audit process. With its automated functionality, this tool efficiently compares coder-assigned codes to auditor-assigned codes, generating audit outcomes for various aspects including code accuracy, POA (Present on Admission) changes, abstraction correctness, and DRG (Diagnosis-Related Group) adjustments.&#xA;Beyond auditing, the module facilitates tracking of training recommendations, enabling continuous improvement in coding accuracy and proficiency. Additionally, its built-in section for rebuttal workflow tracking ensures transparent communication and resolution of discrepancies between auditors and coders, ultimately fostering a collaborative and quality-driven coding environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Administrative User Guide</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/administrative-user-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/administrative-user-guide/</guid>
      <description>This guide reviews the application from the perspective of an administrator.&#xA;Account Search Calendar View Dashboard User Reports Scheduled Reports Code Set Management User Management Workflow Management Role Management Validation Management Er Em Configuration Page Grid Column Configuration Chat Room Mapping Configuration Form Designer Shortcut Configuration Help Menu Inactivity Timeout Tuning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Definitions</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/definitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/definitions/</guid>
      <description>Admit Reason This is the reason that registration has typed in; this is not the admit reason set by the coder. That information is displayed in the Admit Dx Code field.&#xA;Category A category is a ‘Dolbey’ created field that is used to further specify a patient type, if applicable. At some sites, category might equal patient type while others may have a category that is comprised of multiple fields to create that category. For example, if you would like to report on how many charts a coder completed for inpatient and then define them by LOS, you then have a category to define the difference between LOS patient types or service lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fields</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/fields/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/fields/</guid>
      <description>This section contains an alphabetical list of fields configured to be available in account search, workflow, and account list grid. These fields and their friendly names are set in the grid columns configuration that can be found in the tools menu. The “Grid Column Configuration” page is an administrative page used to identify the columns displayed. This list may not have the full listing of fields as some fields are custom, however the fields listed are the most common.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colors and Symbols</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/colors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/colors/</guid>
      <description>The Fusion CAC 2 application contains a variety of colors and symbols. The following table provides a detailed explanation of the significance associated with each color and symbol.&#xA;E&amp;M Coding Viewer (Navigation Pane) The E&amp;M Coding viewer lettering will turn red if a user added charges and they were not sent outbound. In order to send the charges outbound there is a check box at the bottom of the viewer “Send Charges Outbound” then you must click save or submit. Once charges are sent outbound the viewer text will return to the default color (black).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>This section contains addenums to the Fusion CAC 2.0 manual based on software releases during the 2.XX cycle.&#xA;V2.23 V2.24 V2.25 V2.26 V2.27 V2.28 V2.51 V2.52 V2.53 V2.54 V2.55</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>