<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drg Outcome :: Fusion CAC Documentation</title>
    <link>https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/fields/drg-outcome/</link>
    <description>This section will only display on an inpatient chart.&#xA;Field Field Description MS-DRG Change? This is a yes or no field. If the billing DRG was changed from the previous DRG assignment. N/A is available in the event the auditor wants to list it as not applicable to the audit. Note if the Billing DRG and the APR-DRG as the same there could be duplication of changes reported on this field and the APR-DRG Change field. Reimbursement Change? This is a field that indicates if the billing DRG change resulted in a increase, decrease or no reimbursement change. N/A is available in the event the auditor wants to list it as not applicable to the audit. Reimbursement Change Amount This is a field that indicates if the billing DRG change resulted in a change the amount will be displayed. APR-DRG ROM Change? This is a yes or no field. If the APR-DRG changed resulted in an ROM (Risk of Mortality) change. N/A is available in the event the auditor wants to list it as not applicable to the audit. APR-DRG SOI Change? This is a yes or no field. If the APR-DRG changed resulted in an SOI (Severity of Illness) change. N/A is available in the event the auditor wants to list it as not applicable to the audit. APR-DRG Change? This is a yes or no field. If the APR-DRG was changed from the previous DRG assignment. N/A is available in the event the auditor wants to list it as not applicable to the audit. Note if the Billing DRG and the APR-DRG as the same there could be duplication of changes reported on this field and the MS-DRG field which is the Billing DRG.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dolbeysystems.github.io/fusion-cac-web-docs/fields/drg-outcome/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  </channel>
</rss>